SFU Archives reference and display materials collection
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Portraits, [ca 1960] - 2002; F-247-1; 1.55 m of textual records 1254 photographs 412 contact sheets 137 negatives 56 slides
  - Honorary Degree Recipients, 1964 - 2002; F-247-1-29; 64 cm of textual records 309 photographs 2 contact sheets 66 negatives
    - Bennett, W.A.C; Premier, 1965; F-247-1-29-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
      Creator's original file classification code: Times Photo By Ken Orr.
    - MacDonald, John B., 1965; F-247-1-29-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
      Creator's original file classification code: REP 4683-2.
    - Pearkes, George R.; Major General, 1965; F-247-1-29-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
      Creator's original file classification code: BC Jennings.
    - Peterson, Leslie R.; Minister of Education, [ca 1965] - [ca 1967]; F-247-1-29-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
      Creator's original file classification code: BC Govt.
    - Lord Lovat, Head of the Clan Fraser, 1965; F-247-1-29-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Hogarth, Madge, 1967; F-247-1-29-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
      Creator's original file classification code: Tony Archer.
    - Koerner, Leon, 1967; F-247-1-29-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - McLuhan, Herbert Marshall, 1967; F-247-1-29-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Frederickson, Clarence J., 1968; F-247-1-29-0-9 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - MacMillan, Harvey Reginald, 1968; F-247-1-29-0-10 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Waterman, Max, 1968; F-247-1-29-0-11 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
      Creator's original file classification code: Franz Linder.
    - Khorana, Har Gobind, 1969; F-247-1-29-0-12 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
      Creator's original file classification code: University of Wisconsin.
    - McKenzie, Robert, 1969; F-247-1-29-0-13 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Ronning, Chester A., 1969; F-247-1-29-0-14 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Stevens, Henry H., 1969; F-247-1-29-0-15 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Watt, Kenneth. E.F., 1970; F-247-1-29-0-16 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - George, Chief Dan, 1971; F-247-1-29-0-17 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Ireland, Willard, 1967 - 1971; F-247-1-29-0-18 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
      Creator's original file classification code: Provincial Archives of BC.
    - Murray, Margaret, 1964 - 1971; F-247-1-29-0-19 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
      Creator's original file classification code: Addington.
    - Ormsby, Margaret, 1971; F-247-1-29-0-20 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Shrum, Gordon, 1971; F-247-1-29-0-21 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Herzberg, Gerhard, 1972; F-247-1-29-0-22 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - MacInnis, Grace, 1972; F-247-1-29-0-23 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - McTaggart-Cowan, Patrick D., 1972; F-247-1-29-0-24 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Colville, David Alexander, 1973; F-247-1-29-0-25 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Erickson, Arthur, 1965 - 1973; F-247-1-29-0-26 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Smith, Gordon A., 1973 - 1976; F-247-1-29-0-27 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
      Creator's original file classification code: Vancouver Art Gallery.
    - Diamond, Jack, [ca 1974]; F-247-1-29-0-28 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Wilson, John O., 1964 - 1974; F-247-1-29-0-29 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Winch, Harold, 1974; F-247-1-29-0-30 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Branca, Angelo, 1975 - 1984; F-247-1-29-0-31 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Laskin, Bora, 1975; F-247-1-29-0-32 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
      Creator's original file classification code: Canadian Press.
    - Nemetz, Nathaniel, 1975; F-247-1-29-0-33 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Proudfoot, Patricia M., 1975; F-247-1-29-0-34 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Lachs, Manfred, 1976; F-247-1-29-0-35 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Caple, Kenneth, 1977; F-247-1-29-0-36 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Lane, Elizabeth, [ca 1976] - [ca 1977]; F-247-1-29-0-37 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Lawrence, Margaret, 1977; F-247-1-29-0-38 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
      Creator's original file classification code: Eldie Steiner (IMC).
    - Wiliams, Guy R., [ca 1974] - [ca 1977]; F-247-1-29-0-39 (Archival box - standard 247-8)
    - Christensen, Jorgen Vibe, 1978; F-247-1-29-0-40 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Halpern, Ida, 1978; F-247-1-29-0-41 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Hean-Chatterton, Arnold, 1978; F-247-1-29-0-42 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Sandwell, Percy, [ca 1965] - [ca 1978]; F-247-1-29-0-43 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
      Creator's original file classification code: Who's Who International Press.
    - Shadbolt, Jack, [ca 1966] - [ca 1978]; F-247-1-29-0-44 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Wilson, John Tuzo, [ca 1966] - [ca 1978]; F-247-1-29-0-45 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
      Creator's original file classification code: UNS, IMC.
    - Adaskin, Harry, 1979; F-247-1-29-0-46 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Berger, Thomas R., 1979; F-247-1-29-0-47 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - McLean, Cyrus, 1979; F-247-1-29-0-48 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Prittie, Robert, 1979; F-247-1-29-0-49 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Thompson, Syd, 1979; F-247-1-29-0-50 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Hoar, William, 1980; F-247-1-29-0-51 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
      Creator's original file classification code: Jennings.
    - Koerner, Iby, 1980; F-247-1-29-0-52 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
      Creator's original file classification code: Valnor Studios.
    - Lett, Evelyn, 1980; F-247-1-29-0-53 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
      Creator's original file classification code: Campbell.
    - MacNeish, Richard, 1980; F-247-1-29-0-54 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Meredith, John, [ca 1971] - [ca 1980]; F-247-1-29-0-55 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Scott, Francis, 1980; F-247-1-29-0-56 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
      Creator's original file classification code: Lois Lord, NY.
    - Armstrong, Elsje, 1981; F-247-1-29-0-57 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Bunge, Mario Augusto, 1981; F-247-1-29-0-58 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Currie, Lauchlin, 1981; F-247-1-29-0-59 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - McTaggart-Cowan, Ian, 1981; F-247-1-29-0-60 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Miranda, Louis, 1981; F-247-1-29-0-61 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
      Creator's original file classification code: M Comment - spring.
    - Atherley, Gordon R.C., 1982; F-247-1-29-0-62 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Gilles, James, 1982; F-247-1-29-0-63 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Hamilton, William McLean, 1982; F-247-1-29-0-64 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Lambert, Allen T., 1982; F-247-1-29-0-65 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - McArthur, John, 1982; F-247-1-29-0-66 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Rogers, Robert, 1982; F-247-1-29-0-67 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Stevenson, Anne M., 1982; F-247-1-29-0-68 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Wilson, Edward O., 1982; F-247-1-29-0-69 (Archival box - standard 247-9)
    - Belkin, Morris, 1983; F-247-1-29-0-70 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Emmott, Alan Herbert, 1983; F-247-1-29-0-71 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Goodlad, John Inkster, 1983; F-247-1-29-0-72 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Strand, Kenneth Thomas, 1972 - 1983; F-247-1-29-0-73 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
      Creator's original file classification code: AVC 6472-31, IMC 83039.
    - Webster, John Edgar, 1983; F-247-1-29-0-74 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
      Creator's original file classification code: Steve Terrel, Phil Hersee.
    - Beinder, Frank, 1984; F-247-1-29-0-75 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Evans, Hubert R., 1984; F-247-1-29-0-76 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Gunning, Harry Emmet, 1984; F-247-1-29-0-77 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Schreyer, Edward R., 1984; F-247-1-29-0-78 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Evans, Harry MacDonald, 1985; F-247-1-29-0-79 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Friesen, John K., 1985; F-247-1-29-0-80 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Hartley, Fred Lloyd, 1983 - 1985; F-247-1-29-0-81 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
      Creator's original file classification code: Atkinson, IMC.
    - Pentland, Barbara, 1985; F-247-1-29-0-82 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Reuber, Grant Louis, 1985; F-247-1-29-0-83 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
      Creator's original file classification code: V. Tony Hauser.
    - Roche, Douglas James, 1985; F-247-1-29-0-84 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Barrett, David, 1978 - 1986; F-247-1-29-0-85 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
      Creator's original file classification code: IMC, Pete Oloff, UNS.
    - Bene, John Gustav, 1986; F-247-1-29-0-86 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Duckworth, Muriel Helena, 1986; F-247-1-29-0-87 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Eyre, Alan Murray, 1986; F-247-1-29-0-88 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Koshland, Daniel Edward Jr., 1986; F-247-1-29-0-89 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Bligh, John, 1987; F-247-1-29-0-90 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Cote, Paul Thomas, 1987; F-247-1-29-0-91 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Franklin, Ursula Martius, 1987 - 1994; F-247-1-29-0-92 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Gutteridge, May Cecilia, 1987; F-247-1-29-0-93 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Livesay, Dorothy, 1987; F-247-1-29-0-94 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Rust, Thomas Grant, 1987; F-247-1-29-0-95 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - McClelland, Jack Gordon, 1988; F-247-1-29-0-96 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Moonen, Fred Hubert, 1988; F-247-1-29-0-97 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Segal, Joseph, 1987 - 1988; F-247-1-29-0-98 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Slabbert, Frederik Van Zyl, 1988; F-247-1-29-0-99 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Belzberg, Samuel, 1989; F-247-1-29-0-100 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Forrester, Maureen, 1989; F-247-1-29-0-101 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Fouks, Arthur, 1989; F-247-1-29-0-102 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Frum, Barbara, 1989; F-247-1-29-0-103 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Maillet, Antonine, 1989; F-247-1-29-0-104 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Parkinson, Raymond, 1989; F-247-1-29-0-105 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Dye, Kenneth Malcolm, 1990; F-247-1-29-0-106 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Kenney-Wallace, Geraldine Anne, 1990; F-247-1-29-0-107 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Page, Patricia Kathleen, 1990; F-247-1-29-0-108 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Petch, Howard Earle, 1990; F-247-1-29-0-109 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Baker, Ronald J., 1990; F-247-1-29-0-110 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Gzowski, Peter, 1990; F-247-1-29-0-111 (Archival box - standard 247-10)
    - Boyd, Liona, 1991; F-247-1-29-0-112 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Cotler, Irwin, 1991; F-247-1-29-0-113 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Filer, Mary and Harold Spence-Sales, 1991; F-247-1-29-0-114 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
      Creator's original file classification code: Eliza Massey.
    - Jewett, Pauline, 1991; F-247-1-29-0-115 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
      Creator's original file classification code: F.R. LeClair.
    - Lam, David and Dorothy, 1991; F-247-1-29-0-116 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Rowland, F. Sherwood, 1991; F-247-1-29-0-117 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Douglas, James Jardine, 1991; F-247-1-29-0-118 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Eppich, Helmut, 1991; F-247-1-29-0-119 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Eppich, Hugo, 1991; F-247-1-29-0-120 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Reid, Bill, 1991; F-247-1-29-0-121 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Honorary Degree Recipients, 1991 - negatives, F-247-1-29-0-122 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Culver, Dennis Falconer, 1992; F-247-1-29-0-123 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Ellis, A. John, 1992; F-247-1-29-0-124 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Halperin, Maurice, 1992; F-247-1-29-0-125 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Simons, Thomas Allen, 1992; F-247-1-29-0-126 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Tennant, Veronica, 1992; F-247-1-29-0-127 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - August, Aimee, 1992; F-247-1-29-0-128 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Smith, John Maynard, 1992; F-247-1-29-0-129 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
      Creator's original file classification code: M&PR, Archives.
    - Bartlett, Neil, 1993; F-247-1-29-0-130 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
      Creator's original file classification code: Lawrence Berkeley Lab.
    - Bursill-Hall, Geoffrey L., 1993; F-247-1-29-0-131 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
      Creator's original file classification code: Woodwards, West Vancouver.
    - Connell, Martin P., 1993; F-247-1-29-0-132 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Hudson, Donald J., 1993; F-247-1-29-0-133 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Kimura, Doreen, 1993; F-247-1-29-0-134 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Kogawa, Joy Nozomi, 1993; F-247-1-29-0-135 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Lewis, Stephen, 1993; F-247-1-29-0-136 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
      Creator's original file classification code: Spark Studios, Kingston.
    - Coghill, Joy, 1994; F-247-1-29-0-137 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Davidson, Robert, 1994; F-247-1-29-0-138 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Phelps, Michael, 1994; F-247-1-29-0-139 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Shadbolt, Doris, 1994; F-247-1-29-0-140 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Gelbart, Dan, 1994; F-247-1-29-0-141 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Smith, Michael, 1994; F-247-1-29-0-142 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Thomas, Audrey, 1994; F-247-1-29-0-143 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Honorary Degree Recipients, 1994 - negatives, F-247-1-29-0-144 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Campagnolo, Iona, 1995; F-247-1-29-0-145 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Fellegi, Ivan, 1995; F-247-1-29-0-146 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - McDonald, Wendy, 1995; F-247-1-29-0-147 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Norris, Len, 1995; F-247-1-29-0-148 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Nuytten, Phil, 1995; F-247-1-29-0-149 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Vogt, Erich, 1996; F-247-1-29-0-150 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Yu, Wei, 1996; F-247-1-29-0-151 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Laidler, Keith, 1997; F-247-1-29-0-152 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - McCarthy, Grace, 1997; F-247-1-29-0-153 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - McDonald, Hugh, 1997; F-247-1-29-0-154 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Saywell, William, 1997; F-247-1-29-0-155 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Schafer, Murray, 1997; F-247-1-29-0-156 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Anderson, Doris, 1997; F-247-1-29-0-157 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Ballard, Geoffrey, 1997; F-247-1-29-0-158 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Mintzberg, Henry, 1997; F-247-1-29-0-159 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Honorary Degree Recipients, 1998 - textual, 1998 - 1999; F-247-1-29-0-160 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Carkner, Robert, 1998; F-247-1-29-0-161 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Hagan, Stan, 1998; F-247-1-29-0-162 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Overhauser, Albert, 1998; F-247-1-29-0-163 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Rae, Barbara, 1998; F-247-1-29-0-164 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Rieckhoff, Klaus, 1998; F-247-1-29-0-165 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Wong, Milton, 1998 - 2000; F-247-1-29-0-166 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Honorary Degree Recipients, 1999 - textual, F-247-1-29-0-167 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Diamond, Gordon, 1999; F-247-1-29-0-168 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Duthie, Celia, 1999; F-247-1-29-0-169 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Eng, Peter, 1999; F-247-1-29-0-170 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Fraser, John, 1999; F-247-1-29-0-171 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Levy, Julia, 1999; F-247-1-29-0-172 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Mattrick, Don, 1999; F-247-1-29-0-173 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - MacDonald, John S., 1999; F-247-1-29-0-174 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Strate, Grant, 1999; F-247-1-29-0-175 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Honorary Degree Recipients, 2000 - negatives, text, F-247-1-29-0-176 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Broadbent, Ed, 1997 - 2000; F-247-1-29-0-177 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Gosnell, Chief Joseph, 2000; F-247-1-29-0-178 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Marcuse, Judith, 2000; F-247-1-29-0-179 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - McLachlin, Beverley, 2000; F-247-1-29-0-180 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Payette, Julie, 2000; F-247-1-29-0-181 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Spencer, Kenneth, 2000; F-247-1-29-0-182 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Suzuki, David, 2000; F-247-1-29-0-183 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Kerr, Jake, 2000; F-247-1-29-0-184 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Saul, John Ralston, 2000; F-247-1-29-0-185 (Archival box - standard 247-11)
    - Maiman, Theodore, 2002; F-247-1-29-0-186 (Archival box - standard 247-12)
    - Oberlander, Cornelia, 2002; F-247-1-29-0-187 (Archival box - standard 247-12)
    - Segal, Rosalie, 2002; F-247-1-29-0-188 (Archival box - standard 247-12)
    - Ling, Victor, 2002; F-247-1-29-0-189 (Archival box - standard 247-12)
    - Reid, Angus, 2002; F-247-1-29-0-190 (Archival box - standard 247-12)
    - Taylor, Carole, 2002; F-247-1-29-0-191 (Archival box - standard 247-12)
    - Tilghman, Shirley, 2002; F-247-1-29-0-192 (Archival box - standard 247-12)
    - Tong, Kooi Ong, 2002; F-247-1-29-0-193 (Archival box - standard 247-12)
- Sports Photographs, 1950 - 1980; F-247-2; 50 cm of textual records 972 photographs 73 contact sheets 81 negatives 26 slides
  Series consists of photographic materials relating to SFU athletics, athletes, and events that include basketball, football, soccer, swimming, track and field, women's athletics, wrestling, and other miscellaneous sports such as cricket, fencing, hockey, and rugby.
  Department of Athletics
  - Basketball, 1965 - 1980; F-247-2-1; 4 cm of textual records 133 photographs 18 contact sheets 2 negatives
    Series consists of photographic material relating to the SFU basketball program that includes athletic events, practices, and both individual and team photos.
    - SFU vs. Portland State (game, action shots), 1978; F-247-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-1-1. Creator's original file classification code: Vancouver Sun.
    - Basketball Photographs (games, action shots), [ca 1970] - [ca 1978]; F-247-2-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-1-2.
    - Basketball Photographs (team photo, individual group action shots), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-1-3.
    - Basketball Photographs (individual and group shots), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-1-4. Creator's original file classification code: Bill Cunningham.
    - Basketball Photographs (game, action, crowd shots), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-1-5. Creator's original file classification code: Kent Kallberg, Lawrence Feuer.
    - Basketball Photographs - Miscellaneous, [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-1-6. Creator's original file classification code: Peak: Donovan; Bill Cunningham.
  - Football, 1965 - 1980; F-247-2-2; 8 cm of textual records 108 photographs 18 contact sheets 8 negatives
    Series consists of photographic material relating to the SFU football program that includes athletic events, practices, and both individual and team photos.
    - Football (negatives, head shots), [ca 1976] - [ca 1978]; F-247-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-2-1. Creator's original file classification code: West Coast Graphics Photo Services.
    - Football Group Photographs, [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-2-2. Creator's original file classification code: Bill Cunningham.
    - Football Photographs (head, action shots), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-2-3. Creator's original file classification code: West Coast Graphics Photo Services.
    - Football Shrum Bowl Photographs, 1978 - 1979; F-247-2-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-2-4.
    - Football Photographs - Marc Stevenson, [ca 1973]; F-247-2-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-2-5. Creator's original file classification code: West Coast Graphics Photo Services; Bill Cunningham.
    - Football Contact Sheets, [ca 1979]; F-247-2-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-2-6. Creator's original file classification code: West Coast Graphics Photo Services; Bill Cunningham.
    - Football Photographs (head shots), 1976 - 1978; F-247-2-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-2-7.
    - Football Photographs (group, individual shots), 1976 - 1978; F-247-2-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-2-8.
    - Football Photographs (mostly action shots), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-2-9. Creator's original file classification code: Vancouver Sun, Province (David Clark, John Denniston), Columbian (Craig Hodge, Peter Battistoni), Bill Cunningham, Ian Lindsay, B. Taylor.
    - Football Photographs (individual, action shots), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-2-10.
    - Football Photographs (individual, practice shots), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-2-11. Creator's original file classification code: UNS, Bill Cunningham.
    - Simon Fraser Clan Sports Calendar (2), 1978 - 1979; F-247-2-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 247-13)
  - Soccer, 1965 - 1980; F-247-2-3; 6 cm of textual records 111 photographs 11 contact sheets 1 negative
    Series consists of photographic material relating to the SFU soccer program that includes athletic events, practices, and both individual and team photos.
    - Soccer Photographs (portraits), [ca 1965] - [ca 1980]; F-247-2-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 247-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-3-1.
    - Soccer Photographs (portraits, action), [ca 1975]; F-247-2-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 247-14)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: D-4-3-2. Creator's original file classification code: Bill Cunningham.